Guide to the Wunderman Archives, 1946-2010 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1946-2003 and undated, (122 boxes)
  - Sports Illustrated (Box 68)
    - Main Event; Street Scenes; 1 Size Fits All. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 12:00 (Box 68)
    - Miami Dolphins; Pittsburgh Steelers. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 68)
    - Mind Games; NFL Choice; Dream Team. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 68)
    - Mind Read. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 68)
    - Mr. Butkus. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 68)
    - Mr. Christmas; How to Shop for Christmas. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 68)
    - Multi-reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 68)
    - North Carolina. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 68)
    - N. Y. Giants. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 2:00(2 copies) (Box 68)
    - Olympic Christmas. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 68)
    - Philadelphia/Year in Sports; 1992. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 68)
    - Phone Store; Video Store. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 24:00 (Box 68)
    - Pro Football Special. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 68)
  - Sports Illustrated (Box 69)
    - Referee School. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 69)
    - Referee School; Video Store. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 69)
    - Ripping Papers; Feelings/Facts. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 4:00(2 copies) (Box 69)
    - Rosie. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 69)
    - Serious Fans. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 69)
    - She Got Thrill. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 69)
    - Sig/Slams and Card. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 69)
    - Sneak Preview. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 69)
    - Sneaker Store. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 69)
    - Son of Night Stalker. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 69)
    - Special Announcement. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 69)
    - Sports Bag. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 69)
    - Sports Hotline. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 1:30(2 copies) (Box 69)
  - Sports Illustrated (Box 70)
    - Staying on Top. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 70)
    - Sugar Bowl. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 70)
    - Superstar Control. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 70)
    - Tell Her; Mind Read. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 70)
    - The Harmons. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 18:00 (Box 70)
    - The Harmons. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 70)
    - Thriller; New Dunks. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 70)
    - Timings; Gift. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 70)
    - Timing; Results; Signatures; Chronology. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:30 (Box 70)
    - Top Cats. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 1:00(2 copies) (Box 70)
    - Total Access. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 70)
    - Tyson Fight Card. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 70)
    - Untitled commercial. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 70)
    - Various: Sneak Preview; Doubt; Sneaker; Dazzling Dunks. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 28:00 (Box 70)
  - Sports Illustrated (Box 71)
    - Various: 49ers Superbowl. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 28:00 (Box 71)
    - Various: Nebrask National Champs. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 71)
    - Video Party: Bif Bam Boom. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 71)
    - Video Party: Super Duper Baseball Bloopers. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 71)
    - Video Store/Follies; Sneak Preview. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 71)
    - Video Store: NFL Hits. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 71)
    - When It Was Game. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 71)
    - Wired for Sound; Ripping Papers. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 71)
    - Xmas. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 71)
    - Xmas RO-2. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 71)
    - Xmas Story Year in Sports; Mind Readers; Tell Her. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 71)
    - Year in Sports. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 2:30 (Box 71)
    - Year in Sports. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 71)
  - Sports Illustrated for Kids
    - Kids; Read. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 8:00(2 copies) (Box 71)
  - Sports Illustrated for Kids (Box 72)
    - Parents. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 72)
  - Starmedia. 2 spots (Spanish and Portuguese). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 72)
  - Stephen Kessler. Birch Street Gym. Undated. VHS. TRT: 120:00 (Box 72)
  - Sun Direct Insurance (Australia)
    - Compile. Undated. VHS. TRT: 10:00 (Box 72)
    - Mrs. Hadlow. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 0:30(2 copies) (Box 72)
    - Spots. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 72)
    - Spots. 1996. Betacam SP. NTSC. TRT: 5:00 (Box 72)
    - Spots. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 0:45 (Box 72)
    - Spots. 1997. Betacam SP. NTSC. TRT: 0:45 (Box 72)
    - TV commercials. 1995. VHS. TRT: 2:00 (Box 72)
  - Sunkist. Gremlins II trade video. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 4:30 (Box 72)
  - Supermarket Insights
    - Executive Edition: County Market Profile; Pulse of ECR; SI Forum; SI Global Report; IRI Corner. 1994. VHS. PAL. TRT: 30:00 (Box 72)
    - Special Report: Targeting Critical Trends within the Food Distribution Industry. Kraft General Foods: Price Segmentation, Balancing Ice Cream's Turns and Profits. 1993. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 72)
    - Video Category Review: Yogurt, The Cultural Revolution. Kraft General Foods. 1992. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 72)
  - Swiss Colony
    - Early; Combo; Wheel Early; Fruit Cake; Assortment; Late 60. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 15:00 (Box 72)
    - Fireside; Mouse Poster; Long Early Bird; Heavens; Short Bird Lift; Readers Digest. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 72)
    - Free Catalog/Free Cheese. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 72)
    - Heavens; Long Early Bird; Short Bird Lift; Fireside; Mouse Poster; Readers Digest. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 72)
    - Sunday Daily Papers. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 72)
  - Swiss Colony (Box 73)
    - TV Guide/Tabloid Insert/Cat/In Home. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 10:00(2 copies) (Box 73)
  - Sydney Saga Holidays (Australia). Spot. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 73)
  - Tabcorp. Sports Betting: Wanna Bet On It? 1997. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 0:30(2 copies) (Box 73)
  - Taco Bell
    - See the Music. 1991. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 0:45 (Box 73)
    - Star Wars promotion: Winneker presentation. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 5:00(2 copies) (Box 73)
    - Taco Bell Today video magazine. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 73)
  - Teach for America. Avid On-Line. 1997. Umatic. TRT: 6:22 (Box 73)
  - Ted Bates Advertising. 17 spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 73)
  - TED Conferences. TEDSell presentation discs. 1996. CD-ROM. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 73)
  - Telecom Xtra
    - 7 spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 73)
    - 7 spots. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 10:00 (Box 73)
    - 2 spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 73)
  - Tetra Pak. Commercials (Bogota, Moscow). Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 74)
  - The Great Yogo Heist (Australia). Spot. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 0:30(2 copies) (Box 74)
  - the Scholarship Book. Spots. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 74)
  - The Television Register (England). Direct Line commercials. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 74)
  - Time, Inc
    - 60 Years. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 74)
    - How'd They Do It? 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 74)
    - Moment in Time; It's For Me. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 74)
    - No Matter Where You Live. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 74)
    - Sports, Inc. animatics. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 74)
  - Time-Life Books
    - 7 spots: Real People; Vincent Price; Epic of Flight; Vietnam Library; Vietnam Experience; Old West. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 14:00(2 copies) (Box 74)
    - American Country. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 74)
    - American Country. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 74)
    - American Country Christmas. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 74)
  - Time-Life Books (Box 75)
    - Animatics. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 75)
    - Captain's Cabin. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 75)
    - Christmas Faces. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 75)
    - Civil War: Gettysburg. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 75)
    - Civil War: Secedes. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 75)
    - Computers. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 75)
    - Computers; Understanding Computers. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 75)
    - Demolition Family. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 75)
    - Designing Your Garden; Perennials. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 75)
    - Direct Response TV: 24 commercials. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box 75)
    - Dismissed; Orson Welles Boobie Chew. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 75)
    - Enchanted World: Animals; Climb. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 75)
    - Enchanted World: Curl Up with the Papers. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 75)
    - Enchanted World: Superstitious Origins. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 75)
    - Enchanted World: You May Never Return. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 75)
  - Time-Life Books (Box 76)
    - Epic of Flight: 21 spots. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 42:00 (Box 76)
    - Epic of Flight: Bomber Run. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 76)
    - Epic of Flight: Bomber Run. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 76)
    - Epic of Flight: Carrier War. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 76)
    - Epic of Flight: Fighting Jets. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 76)
    - Fix It Couple. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 76)
    - Fix It Simple. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 76)
    - Fix It Yourself Couple; Old West, Jack Palance; Enchanted World; Vietnam Experience. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 12:00 (Box 76)
    - Fix It Yourself: Very Simple; The Drip; Easy Way. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 76)
    - Fix It Yourself: Zap. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 76)
    - Forces of the Planet. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 76)
    - Forces of the Planet; Earthquake. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:30 (Box 76)
    - Forces of the Planet non-premium. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 76)
    - Good Cook: Adventure/Poultry; Adventure/Cakes. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 76)
    - Good Cook: Ann's Apron; Home Repair. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 76)
  - Time-Life Books (Box 77)
    - Good Cook: Cooking Demonstration. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 77)
    - Good Cook: Great Chefs. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 77)
    - Good Cook: Poultry. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 77)
    - Good Cook: Serious. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 4:30 (Box 77)
    - Great Ages of Man. 1978. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 77)
    - Great Meals in Minutes: Man; Woman. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 6:00(2 copies) (Box 77)
    - Healthy Home Cooking. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 77)
    - Healthy Home Cooking: Garden. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 77)
    - Home Improvement Library: Cards and Letters. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 77)
    - Home Repair. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 77)
    - Home Repair: Can You Do This; Plumbing; New Living Spaces; Basic Wiring. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 8:00(2 copies) (Box 77)
    - Home Repair: Home Repair; Home Repair Vila; Kitchens and Bathrooms; New Living Spaces. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 77)
    - Home Repair: If I Had a Hammer; Home Repair Bob Vila. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 77)
  - Time-Life Books (Box 78)
    - Home Repair: One Man Job. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 78)
    - Home Repair: Stop Saying Support. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 78)
    - Home Repair: Strobe Hammer. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 78)
    - Home Repair: Surprise K&B. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 2:00(2 copies) (Box 78)
    - Home Repair: Vila/Dreamhouse; Fix-It Vila Testimonial. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 78)
    - Home Repair: Wiring; Plumbing. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 78)
    - Home Repair: You Can Do It; Do It. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 78)
    - Home Repairs; Civil War. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 78)
    - How Could It Happen; Knowing Them. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 78)
    - Library of Curious and Unusual Facts. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 78)
    - Martial Arts Expert. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 78)
    - Mysteries Dismissed. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 78)
    - Mysteries of the Unknown: Explain It. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 78)
    - Mysteries of the Unknown: Explain It. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 78)
  - Time-Life Books (Box 79)
    - Nazis. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 79)
    - Library of Curious and Unusual Facts: Imagine. 1990. 1" video reel. TRT: 4:30 (Box 79)
    - Mysteries of the Unknown: Dismissed Mystic Places. 1987-1989. 1" video reel. TRT: 2:00(2 reels) (Box 79)
    - Mysteries of the Unknown: Explain It. 1988-1989. 1" video reel. TRT: 2:00(4 reels) (Box 79)
    - Old West: Belt Buckle. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 79)
    - Old West: Ghost Saloon. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 79)
    - Pasta Wrap Serious. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 79)
    - Planet Earth: Two Farmers. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 1:40 (Box 79)
  - Time-Life Books (Box 80)
    - Push Ups; Thermogram. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 80)
    - Real Joe If You Can Intro. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 80)
    - Real People: Vincent Price Ghost. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 80)
    - Secret War. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 80)
    - Secret War. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 80)
    - Seeing the Unseen. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 1:20 (Box 80)
    - Third Reich: Personalities. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 2:00(2 copies) (Box 80)
    - Third Reich: Tomorrow; Excuses; Personalities. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 80)
    - Third Reich: Violinist; Personalities. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 80)
    - Understanding Computers: Lend a Hand. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 80)
    - Vietnam Experience: Slow Motion; Flag. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 80)
    - Vietnam Experience: These Were the Times. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 80)
    - Vietnam Library: Real Soldiers. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 80)
    - Vietnam Series: Dear America. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 80)
  - Time-Life Books (Box 81)
    - Voyage. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 81)
    - Voyage Through the Universe. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 81)
    - What's Vietnam? 1987. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 81)
    - You've got It Made. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 7:00 (Box 81)
    - 6 spots: Momentary Madness; Not Necessarily the News; Greatest Moments 60s. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 81)
    - 9 spots: Time Flies. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 18:00 (Box 81)
    - 10 spots: Expecting You; Reader; Time Flies; 1986. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 81)
    - 10 spots: Ultronic Comm.; Designer Phone; Phone Globe; Phone Memoboard; Cassette Deck; Desk; Great Moments 60s; Time Man; Fab Century Book; Coffee Maker. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 81)
    - 1890--A New Year. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 81)
    - All Year Long. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 81)
    - Almanac premium. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 81)
    - Almanac update; Election Pitch. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 81)
    - American Presidents; Horseback; President. 1976. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 81)
    - Ask Me Anything. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 81)
    - Atlas. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 81)
  - Time Magazine (Box 82)
    - Atlas of the Body. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 82)
    - Bookstore. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 82)
    - Building the Phone. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 82)
    - Building the Phone II. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 82)
    - Christmas Faces. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 82)
    - Don't Miss 1980. 1979. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 82)
    - Editorial Room. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 82)
    - Enchanted World; Time Flies. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 82)
    - Faces '82. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 82)
    - Faces '82; Anticipation. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 82)
    - Fall '80 Atlas. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 82)
    - Fireplace '81. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 9:00 (Box 82)
    - Gorbachev; Ethics; Leadership. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 82)
    - Hard Sell. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 82)
    - Historical tape: 15 commercials. 1986-1987. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 82)
  - Time Magazine (Box 83)
    - I Understand. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 83)
    - I'll Take It. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 83)
    - I'll Take It; Reason. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 83)
    - I'll Take It; Time Flies. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 83)
    - It's For Me. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 83)
    - It's Here Someplace. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 83)
    - Jan. '81 preprint support. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 83)
    - Jenny/FM Radio--Liberty Pin. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 83)
    - JFK; LBJ; CNN Year in Review; 80s Greed Decade. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 83)
    - Kitchen; Professor. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 83)
    - Magazine with Everything; Time Flies. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 83)
    - Magazine with Everything; Time Flies. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 2:00(2 copies) (Box 83)
    - Magazine with Everything; Time Flies. 1983. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 83)
    - Meet the Mailman. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 83)
  - Time Magazine (Box 84)
    - Moment of Time. 1988. 1" video reel. TRT: Undetermined. (Box 84)
    - Moment of Time; It's For Me. 1987. 1" video reel. TRT: 4:00 (Box 84)
    - Moment of Time; It's For Me. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 84)
    - Nancy. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 84)
    - News Bureaus. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 84)
    - No Matter Where You Live; What's In the Box; I'll Take It Again. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 84)
    - Participate. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 84)
    - Premium tester spots: 14 spots. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 18:00 (Box 84)
    - Search; Be Right Back. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 12:00 (Box 84)
    - Selected direct response tv commercials. 1978-1979. Umatic. TRT: 26:00 (Box 84)
    - Sons; Walkabout; I Understand. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 84)
    - The News. 1980. Umatic. TRT: 8:00 (Box 84)
  - Time Magazine (Box 85)
    - The Trunk. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 85)
    - The Trunk. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 85)
    - Throw Away. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies; Deluge; Avalanche. 1984. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies; Magazine with Everything. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies; After the Deluge; Ill Fated Tanker; Newsfolks; Revolving Door. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies reel 2: 20 spots. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 40:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies, Saturday Night Live version. 1985. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies; Turn Turn Turn. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 18:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies with alternate wrap, spots 2-26. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 60:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies with wrap. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 85)
    - Time Flies with wrap clock phone: 26 spots. 1986. Umatic. TRT: 52:00 (Box 85)
    - Time in a Bottle. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 85)
    - Time in a Bottle; Wilderness; I'll Take It; Time Flies; It's Here Someplace; Time Has Come; Time Well Spent; Turn Turn Turn; Premium Time; Not for Sale; Gorbachev; Ethics; Leadership. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 26:00 (Box 85)
    - Time in a Shorter Bottle. 1981. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 85)
  - Time Magazine (Box 86)
    - Turn Turn Turn. 1987. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 86)
    - Turn Turn Turn. 1987-1988. Umatic. TRT: 8:00(2 copies) (Box 86)
    - Untitled commercial. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 86)
    - Why Not Subscribe; Magazine with Everything; Pac Man; Time Quiz; Wilderness. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 86)
    - Wilderness. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 86)
    - Wilderness/Bookends. 1982. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 86)
    - Year in Review. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 86)
  - Time-Warner, Inc
    - Life Magazine: Africa. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 14:00 (Box 86)
    - Life Magazine: Moments--Nature. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 86)
    - Life Magazine: Moments--Nature; Camelot. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 4:00 (Box 86)
  - Tops Markets. How Amazing; How Picky; How Lean. 1996. VHS. TRT: 1:30 (Box 86)
  - Toys R Us. Spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:00 (Box 86)
  - Travelers Insurance. Current Travelers Group Advertising. 1998. Umatic. TRT: 2:45 (Box 86)
  - Turner Entertainment. Best of MGM/UA Home Video: Autant en Emporte Le Vent (Gone With The Wind). 1990. VHS. TRT: 214:00 (Box 86)
  - Tut Totes (Box 87)
    - Direct Marketing Workshop. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 87)
    - Spots. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 87)
    - WRK house copy. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 87)
  - TV Fuji. Millennium Campaign with Mr. Bean (WCJ Frankfurt). Undated. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 1:30 (Box 87)
  - TV Guide
    - Anthea Disney spots. Undated. VHS. TRT: 4:30 (Box 87)
    - Chiat/Day/Mojo spots. Undated. VHS. TRT: 3:00 (Box 87)
    - Commercials. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 87)
    - Decoder Sweepstakes. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 87)
    - TV Discount; Cable Discount. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 87)
    - United Artists spots. Undated. VHS. TRT: 8:30 (Box 87)
  - TVA
    - TVA. O melhor da TV mundial no conforto e segurança da sua casa. WCJ Brasil. Undated. VHS. TRT: 20:00 (Box 87)
    - Wireless Cable TV Paid TV Subscription: Dinorah. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 87)
    - Wireless Cable TV Paid TV Subscription: Dinorah. Undated. Betacam SP. TRT: 1:30 (Box 87)
  - Tyee Productions
    - Breakfast reel. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:00(2 copies) (Box 87)
    - Demo reel. Undated. VHS. TRT: 12:15 (Box 87)
    - Demo reel short version. 1995. VHS. TRT: 7:20(2 copies) (Box 87)
    - Infomercial demo reel. Undated. VHS. TRT: 13:20(2 copies) (Box 87)
    - Infomercial demo reel. 1994. VHS. NTSC. TRT: 15:00 (Box 87)
    - Quick Cut historical reel. Undated. VHS. TRT: 9:04(2 copies) (Box 87)
  - United Airlines. VIF Services Center. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 5:00 (Box 88)
  - United States Army
    - Dear Dad. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 88)
    - Freedom Isn't Free. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
    - Full Time Pride. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
    - Full Time Pride. 1996. D2TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
    - Next Step. 1999. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
    - Survey 11. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 0:15 (Box 88)
    - Tribute. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
    - Uniform. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
    - United States Postal Service (USPS) (Box 88)
    - 1990 Cheers promo. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 10:14 (Box 88)
    - Alaska. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 1:30 (Box 88)
    - All Services: Anthem; Jets; Saturday; Drop Off; Hot Rod Mail; Olympic Sponsorship. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 5:28 (Box 88)
    - Anthem. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 88)
  - United States Postal Service (USPS) (Box 89)
    - BMAU video; New Rates Meeting. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 18:00 (Box 89)
    - BRMAS--Business Reply Mail Accounting System. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:53 (Box 89)
    - Check It Out. 1995. VHS. TRT: 30:00 (Box 89)
    - Complete Addressing Manager's October Event. 1990. VHS. TRT: 30:00(2 copies) (Box 89)
    - Corporate Initiative/Worldpost. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 7:40 (Box 89)
    - Creative reel: 20 spots. 1996. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 89)
    - Dramatic Moments in Olympic Games History--Winning Strategies. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 20:00 (Box 89)
    - Express Mail: Airplane/Letter Carrier; Cloud. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 0:55 (Box 89)
    - Express Mail: Blondie. 1989. Umatic. TRT: 6:00 (Box 89)
    - Express Mail case history. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 89)
    - Express Mail International: Global; Madrid. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 89)
    - Express Mail International: Global Version B. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 89)
    - Express Mail International: Madrid Version B. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 89)
    - Express Mail: Iron Legs; Emerson; Olson; Two/CC; Torch II. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 89)
    - Express Mail: Pick-Up Truck. 1990. Umatic. TRT: 2:00 (Box 89)
  - United States Postal Service (USPS) (Box 90)
    - Express Mail/Priority Mail: Moving Van. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 0:30 (Box 90)
    - Express Mail Sales Service. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 3:30 (Box 90)
    - Express Mail: San Jose Telemarketing. Undated. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 90)
    - Express Mail: Speedy Hub. Priority Mail: Overkill. 1994. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 90)
    - Express Mail Service FY '89 Marketing Video: We Deliver. 1988. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 90)
    - From Cave to Computer: A Short History of Mail Preparation. 1991. Umatic. TRT: 10:00 (Box 90)
    - FSN App. 1995. Umatic. TRT: 30:00 (Box 90)
    - Going Beyond Yabbit. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 40:46 (Box 90)
    - Going Beyond Yabbit. 1992. VHS. TRT: 60:00 (Box 90)
    - Growing Your Business with Advertising Mail. Undated. VHS. TRT: 37:00 (Box 90)
    - Holiday Promotion: When Is a Stamp; Santa's Workshop; Fireplace; Boots and Gloves. 1993. Umatic. TRT: 2:30 (Box 90)
    - Holiday TVCs: Tutus; Fireplace. 1992. Umatic. TRT: 1:00 (Box 90)